# professional summary

I am a full-stack software developer currently located in Atlanta, GA. I have 10+ years experience working with teams and individuals in the social work field and have held multiple leadership roles since 2011. I am seeking to join a collaborative team that focuses on creating meaningful work and aligns with my core values of enthusiasm, growth, and stewardship.

# featured projects

#### **Planted**

- Utilizes arduino and Raspberry Pi to monitor garden conditions. Data is viewed in React Native application.
- Technology Stack: React/React Native, Express, Python, PostgreSQL, GraphQL
- Link: https://github.com/PlantedDC

## **Phantom Closet**

- eCommerce site that allows players of Magic: The Gathering to view, search, and rent cards
- Technology Stack: React/JavaScript, Node.js/Express, PostgreSQL
- Link: https://github.com/codingandcaring/phantomCloset

# experience

**Social Services Administrator**, Georgia Department of Family and Children Services (Cobb County)
May 2017 - January 2018

- Directed a team of 4 social service units in providing quality services to clients
- Worked closely with internal and external stakeholders to plan and implement strategies for improving performance

**Community Clinician**, Northstar Psychological Services September 2016 - May 2017

- Provided clinical services to families and individuals, including counseling and therapeutic interventions
- Collaborated with clients to identify goals and create individualized treatment plans

Family Service Counselor Supervisor, Kids First of Florida March 2013 - June 2016

 Led a team of 6 family service counselors, providing daily oversight, check-ins, and clinical support

**Social Worker**, Georgia Department of Family and Children Services
June 2007 - March 2013

# **Ashley Parker**

(912) 614-2045

ashley@codingandcaring.com codingandcaring.com

### skills

JavaScript
HTML / CSS
Node.js
GitHub
jQuery
Python
RESTful API
Express
PostgreSQL
AWS
React
React Native

## education

Full-Stack Software
Development Bootcamp
May 2018

DigitalCrafts
Atlanta, GA

Master's Degree in Social Work (MSW)

May 2010 Valdosta State University

Bachelor's Degree in Social Work (BSW)

May 2009 Albany State University